Ending
It's time for another episode of UpGod, this time with Yume Kudo of Juice-Juice and Korin Hashimoto of Angulum.
This is a program that takes you behind the scenes of the production of various artists belonging to the Upfront Group.
We will show you the process of recording and rehearsal.
Let's start with a behind-the-scenes look at our two MCs.
I'm Kudo, and we have a new member, Mifu Kawashima.
The first thing all the members asked her was what kind of sun protection she uses.
The first thing the members asked was what kind of sun protection she uses, and she told us that she has been wearing sunscreen since she was a child, which has resulted in her beautiful skin.
When we take a group photo, one of them looks like he is the only one who is glowing in the sun.
By the way, I get burnt like an octopus dumpling every year.
Well, I just put on a little bit of paint and call it a day.
It's true that it's very easy to get burnt this season.
Yes, that's right. You have to be careful.
I guess sunscreen is important.
Do you get sunburned easily?
I get sunburned very easily.
I see.
So good luck with that.
You're right.
Good luck.
Let's do it.
I want to make it through this summer.
My initial speed is...
I felt that during the activities...
When I was choreographing dances...I was choreographing a dance or something.
When we were choreographing the Beast of Love.
When the dance teacher was choreographing
the dance instructor would call out "hoo" or something like that during the song.
during the song.
So we got really excited and enjoyed the choreography.
We enjoyed the choreography.
During the live performance, Mr. Sasaki and others
Mr. Sasaki and others were especially encouraging us.
His voice cheered us up during the live.
It gave us energy and motivation to work harder.
and motivate me to work harder.
I hope I can do that from now on.
I hope I can do that in the future.
That's really good.
Recently, Sakura Ishiyama has been doing
Sakura Ishiyama has been doing a lot of stirring up the crowd
I hope you can join us at our live performance.
so please come to our live concert if you want to see us.
If you like, please come and see them live!
Now, let's see what's up this time!
Let's start from here.
Ochanoma Shekenare Dance Lesson
Released on July 26th!Now released on July 26th!
from the latest single by Tea Norma
Shekenare's dance lesson.
Please take a look
Please.
Okay, first position.
Yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes,  yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes
Pass here, pass here, we've all done this, we'll do this. All of you do this, do this.
Do this, do this, do this.
And then the first person to go around, the second person to go around as before.
One after another.
Next move!
Okay.
Okay, here comes the concert.
Do you know how to play the guitar? Do you know how to ride a guitar like this?
You can play this on the base, on your own, wherever you want to play.
Yes, I got it.
1,2,3,4,5,6,7,8,9,10.
And the hands are slanted, basic.
And this is the middle finger, middle. Downwards.
And I want you to make a slant.
The body is also diagonal.
Yes, the body is also oblique.
Shekilare, shekilare, shekilare.
One, two, three, four.One, two, three, four.
So, the hand starts here, here, here.
Starting here, 1,2,3.
It'll come around here.
Yes, yes, yes.
Tarattatare-tarattatare-tarattatare.
One, two, three.
And both legs, open like this.
And when you put your hands around like a light grip.
Yeah, like this, like this, like this, like this, like this.
With a light grip.
And then open. And then open them from here.
Yes, don't do it like this here, don't do it like this here.
Start here, about 90 degrees to the side of the head.
Two, three.
And then open both legs, sheki, sheki, pause.
Tarattare-tarattare-tarattare.
When you pause properly, stop. Stop.
Something like, bounce.
Ah, yes, that's right.
Not bounce, stop. Stop.
Yeah, stop. Stop firmly.
Par!
Run!
Stop!Stop!
One, two, three, four, clear!
Make a diagonal,
Come on, come on, spread it out!
Oh!
Back up!
I'm walking!
OK!
Yes, thank you.
Pan!
Turn,
La la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la
Then, pan!
And then pan!
And then, pan!
Don't tell me!
Chong!
Tell me!
and,
Heisei no
Beat not lie
Hey.Hey.
Oh, dah.
More, more, more.
Just keep 'em coming.
Serious is serious. Keep it up.
Let's do this.
Here we go.
These are the steps.
Ah!
Pan!
One, two, three, four, five, six, seven, eight. That's the maint.
On the contrary
Ah!
the opposite.
In square...
Yeah, okay, so bread, bread, bread, bread, bread, and the opposite, bread, bread, bread, bread, bread.
This is the same, this is the same.
And after this.
And, stand.
Palm front.
Stand.
Above.
Grip open while holding hands on hips with arms.
Pointing. Pointing.
So, let's go up to the thighs and do a batten cross on the inside.So, let's go to the thigh and do a batten cross on the inside.
Cross it open.
And grip it.
And turn toward your place.
Seeno.
One, two, three, four.
And while lowering this goo.
While lowering it.
Next time
Oh, no, no, no. That could be troublesome.
I can only see a little.
Yeah, you should put on some facial expressions if you can.
Dreams. It happens all the time.
Tip rates for crossing.
Three, two, one.
If you can't afford it, just concentrate on your own movements.
I'm a bit of a mystery.
Dreams you haven't even told your parents about yet
Louder and louder
Stop where you're stopping.
I'm stepping.
If it's with you
Shake it out, a future no one knows
With our hands, we'll open up our Miroki
Let's do it all as we danceLet's do it all as we dance
Hop-step, hop-step Shake it up
Shake it up
Shake it up The power to believe in yourself
Ordinary, but kickin' and rollin'
LALALA
Dance!
One day I'll come to this dance
Now I'm counting up and down
Shake it up
Shake it up to the wind
Shake it up again Shake it up
Wow!
Wow! Waiting game!
The song "Shekenare" is the ending theme of the TV anime "Shadow Bus Frame".
The song has actual lines from the anime.
It's a very cheerful song that will cheer you up.
I hope everyone will listen to it!
And about the dance lesson...
Shekenare's title is "Sheke", which means "sheke" in Japanese.
Sheke-sheke" is the part of the title of the song, and the choreography is designed so that everyone can join in with the choreography.
I hope you will also pay attention to that part of the choreography.
Also, when there is a song in which each individual stands out, we all do the choreography separately.
I hope you will also check out the choreography of the songs in which each individual stands out.
I would be happy if you could check that out as well!I hope you'll check that out too!
I hope you will listen to Shekenare a lot!
Thank you very much.
This song is the ending theme song for the TV Tokyo anime Shadowverse Frame, and I just watched the video of the dance lesson.
The lyrics of the song are very energetic, and the dance instructor's advice to be conscious of facial expressions and to focus on the dance for those who are still full of dancing is very warm and encouraging.
I'm the type of person who is occupied with dancing, so I was grateful to hear the teacher's words.
I think that the facial expressions that I practiced in the dance lessons are also reflected in the music video.
I'd like to work with you again on the actual music video.
The teacher was very particular about the shape of the fingertips, and I wonder if that was the reason why all the dancers' movements looked so cool and coherent.
That was the dance lesson at the tea ceremony!
JYP's new single "Sikenare
Thanks for watching!
Here's the next one. Akari Takeuchi: "I have to go! Vocal Recording!"
It is included in Angulum's latest single. Akari Takeuchi "I gotta go! Please take a look at the vocal recording of "I've got to go!
Are you okay with me doing it already?
I'm fine.
Let's start with the A melody.
From the beginning of a dream to the time I remember it.
I was just a kid when the dream began.
I turned around and saw the road that had been going on for a long time
I cried because I couldn't do it well and I felt unworthy
There was such a thing in the beginning, wasn't there?
I remember.
Okay, okay, okay.
Yeah, that's it.Well, there you have it.
The beginning of a dream is hard.
Okay, but if you can just get there, you'll be fine.
Yes, sir.
I was just a kid when the dream began.
It's been a long time since I looked back.
I couldn't do it the way I came.
I cried because I couldn't do it right.
That's how it started, isn't it?
I remember.
Yeah, okay.
Because you're all that's in front of you, right?
Yes, sir.
That's happened to you, too.
I remember.
It's always a work in progress.
Some nights I get scared.
But you have to go... to find it.
Because you're the only one who can give you the answers.
Okay, okay.
Okay, let's go to the end.
Well, let's just take a quick look.
Because I'm the only one
I sang it over and over without showing it to anyone
I sang it over and over and over againI sang it over and over and over and over again
I wish I could show you now
The future that I dreamed of
The future is shining right here
I have a feeling I'll be able to hear a little more OK
It's OK
Maybe if I let the music take over more
I feel like it could be better. You know what a snare is? I mean, listen to the drums' thump, thump, thump, thump, thump, thump, thump, thump, thump, thump, thump, thump.
I mean, let's listen to it and sing it while listening to it.
I want to sing and show the me of that day now, the future that I dreamed of, the future is shining right here.
Where we kept layering the music. Let's go.
I hope you nod your head.
The little light that kept on lighting up
Became a myriad of floating lights all over the place
They'll start to shimmer and soar
Light up the way Now it's time to step out
It's going to soar
The small light that keeps on shining
It's a myriad of floating lights
They start to shimmer and soar
Light up the way, now it's time to step out
Okay, okay!
Okay, now, just...
High up...
Yeah, I gotta go, I gotta go, I gotta goYeah, I gotta go, I gotta go, I gotta go.
Let's go for the trifecta.
Yes!
The future I dreamed of, the future I dreamed of
I love to sing I love to dance
That's all I ever wanted. That's all I ever wanted.
That's what I wanted to see
The future I dreamed of, the future I dreamed of
I gotta go, I gotta go, I gotta go, I gotta go.
Okay, are you sure? Are you sure?
Okay!
Head, he likes to sing.
Is it coming in singing?
It's just that it would be nice to hear it a little bit more solid here.
Yes, sir!
The future I dreamed of, the future I dreamed of
I love to sing, I love to dance
That's all I ever wanted to do That's all I ever wanted to do
That's what I wanted to see
The future I dreamed of, the future I dreamed of
I gotta go, I gotta go, I gotta go, I gotta go
I'm just going to make a point.
I like to sing, I like to danceHead, I like to sing, I like to dance.
I'm only going here, simply de length
I like to sing, I like to dance
I'm a little short here, so I guess that's it?
I like to sing
Yes, yes!
The future I dreamed of, the future I dreamed of
I like to sing I like to dance
OK!
Yes! That's it!
Yes! Thank you very much!
Yes, that's right. I heard this song directly from Mr. Takeuchi.
When I received this song, the lyrics and the music made me cry.
I couldn't sing it well.
He said he sang it without emotion during the recording.
I wanted to see the recording of the song myself.
I wanted to see how she sang the song, so I was really happy to see it.
But even though she sang without emotion, it sounded like she sang with a lot of emotion.
I thought Takeuchi-san was amazing!
It's not only the technique that you have cultivated over the years of your career, but also the softness and power that you bring to your songs.
but your singing voice, which has both power and softness, is really great.
I also got goosebumps when I heard it at Yokohama Arena.
The venue was really blue!
I was very happy to be able to hear her live, and I was also very happy to be able to see the video of Takeichi-san's recording.
That's all for now, Takeichi Akari, vocal recording of "I gotta go! Akari Takeichi's vocal recording of "I have to go!This is Takeichi Akari's vocal recording of "I gotta go! The above is the vocal recording of Takeichi Akari, "I have to go!
I'm sure you'll be fine as usual.
This is an up-dated paper by Yume Yatoh of Juice-Juice and Rin Yatsoku of Angulum. Here is the next one.
Juice-Juice PRIDE BRIDE VOCAL RECORDING
Here is the vocal recording of Lulu Dambara for Juice-Juice's latest single, PRIDE BRIDE.
Is there anything you don't understand?
No, I don't.
Okay, let's start filming.
Let's start with the first four lines.
Okay, let's start with the first four lines.
So you were with that girl.
I'm not the kind of woman who can compare and say, "Congratulations on being chosen.
Yes, I guess I could do with a little of that emotion.
I think that's all right.
I'm singing about not being a woman, and I'm kind of pulling back now.
I'm not a woman... I'm singing in a withdrawn way now. I think it's okay if I sing it like that.
Okay, let's try it again.
Okay.
You were with that girl, weren't you?
I'm not the kind of woman who can say "Congratulations" for being chosen over another.
Okay.
Only one number one is a
I don't know if it's the B melody, but it's really short.
Let's just do this one.Let's just do this.
I'm not the kind of woman who can say, "Congratulations, you've been chosen for everything.
Only one or number one I fall in love for different reasons
Only one and number one I'm neither
Only one or number one, I fall in love for different reasons
I'd like to see a little more rhythm in the "in love..." part
I'm not the kind of woman who can say "Congratulations, you've been chosen for everything.
Only one or number one I fall in love for different reasons
Only one and number one I'm both
OK, now the chorus?
Yes!
Let's start with the first four times.
Only one and number one, I'm neither
I wanted to love you, but I couldn't. I won't kiss you in harmony.
You couldn't take away my pride, my pride, my pride
Or hold on to it for the last time
I think you should hold on to it with all your might.
I feel like that strength will allow you to show your weakness.
Yes! Let's go!
Only one and number one
I wanted to love you, but I couldn't. I won't kiss you on schedule.
Even you couldn't take away my pride.
Let's hold it! Let's just hold it and try one more time!
I don't know what I'll do, I'll get so excited
Hold me, hold me, hold me!Hold him.
Hold on!
I'll just go here!
I'm not going to kiss you like I'm supposed to.
Even you can't take away my pride. Hold on to it.
OK!
Okay, let's try only one and number one.
Yes!
Only one and number one
No, no, no, look forward
The pride I couldn't give even to you
The last one, Pride, is not a very strong word.
Pride is not a very strong pride.
I think pride is the most important thing for this girl.
I think that pride is the most important thing for her.
I want to convey it more.
I want to convey it to her, or rather, I want to push her the most.
Yes, yes.
Let's try one more time.
Okay, then that's all.
Okay, that's all.
This song is called "Pride Bright," and as the title says, it means "pride shines brightly.
At first glance, you may think that the woman has a strong sense of pride.
The song is about a woman who has a strong sense of pride, but the song also expresses her conflicting feelings of pride that is about to break.
The song has an accent that gives the song a really fast pace, but at the same time it has a conflicted feeling, so I think it is a song that is very strong and has a lot of energy.The song has an accent that is both fast and conflicted, so I hope you'll pay attention to that part of the song.
I hope you will pay attention to these aspects when you listen to the song.
In the recording video of Dambra-san, Taisei-san said that he didn't understand some parts of the song.
When Taisei-san was first asked if there was anything he didn't understand in the recording of Dambra-san's song
I thought it was really cool that he said "I don't know".
He is the type of person who says "I don't think so" before he starts.
That's what made the difference between us.
Also, his facial expression really matches the mood of the song, or the song itself.
I thought he was really cool.
How was it?
You put a lot of emotion into the first note.
I think it's very difficult to put that kind of emotion into the first note.
I think it's really cool.
I also saw the music video for "Pride Bright".
I also watched the music video of "Pride Bright", and I could see the image of a woman with pride.
Everyone's lipstick is red.
I could feel their pride in that.
I'm glad you liked it.
That's all for Juice-Juice Pride Bright Dambaralulu Vocal Recording!
I wanted to love you, but I couldn't
I wouldn't kiss a leven chauffeur
Even you couldn't take it away from me
Juice-Juice Pride Bright
Now on sale!
Looks like you're having a hard time. Take a break.Sounds like a lot of work. Take a break.
It's time to say goodbye to Yume Kudo and Rin Hashidoko. We've seen a lot of different videos this time, but I, Hashidoko, was really impressed by Danbara-san's recording.
I was really impressed by the video of Mr. Danbara's recording. I had the impression that he sings with a lot of emotion on stage, so it was a great learning experience for me to realize that he sings with such emotion from the very beginning.
I, Kudo, have been watching the dance video of Ochamama's Shekenar, and after watching the dance video, I really want to dance too.
I was very happy to hear Akari Takeuchi's piercing voice.
In this issue of Up Paper, we're going to take you behind the scenes of the production of various artists who belong to the Up Front Group.
We'll introduce you the parts you don't usually see, so please subscribe to our channel! This time, Upgami is with Yume Kudo of Juice-Juice and Rin Hayashi of Angeleum.
Yume Kudo of Juice-Juice and Rin Haya of Angeleum.
Next time on Apu-Kami: Angulum's Ai no Kedamono Dance Lesson!
And we will be showing the recording of Juice-Juice's Funky Flash.
Enjoy!